Guide to the Time Inc. Sports Illustrated Publishing and Business Records 1950s-1993 MS 3009-RG 35
New-York Historical Society
- Series IV. Advertising Promotion Department Records, 1950s-1987; 28.1 Linear feet in 29 record cartons, 1 document case, and 1 flat box
  - Subseries VI.A. Special Events and Publicity Director Keith Morris Files, 1957-1980; 20.6 Linear feet in 20 record cartons, 1 document case, and 1 flat box
    - Subsubseries VI.A.4. Recordings of Sports Figures Interviews [RESTRICTED], 1960s-1986; 3.25 Linear feet in 4 record cartons containing 142 items and 2 folders
      - Interviews, 1984 October 22-1985 February 19 (Offsite-box 4124, Item 75-86)
        Gerald Henderson/Seattle Supersonics
      - Interviews, 1984 November 21 (Offsite-box 4126, Item 3)
        1 videocassette (U-matic S)
        New York Islander interviews
        Anders Kallur
        Duane Sutter
        Pat Flatley
        Bryan Trottier
        Pat Lafontaine
      - Interviews, 1984 November 21 (Offsite-box 4126, Item 4)
        Dave Langevin
        Bob Bourne
      - Interviews, 1985 (Offsite-box 4126, Folder 2)
        1 videocassette (U-matic)
        Spring Training Interviews
        Pete Rose/Cincinnati Reds
        Bob Knepper/Houston
        Alan Ashby/Houston
        Jim Kaat/Cincinnati
        Kirk Gibson/Detroit
        Lan Trammell/Detroit
        Len Matuzak/Phillies (traded)
        Claude Osteen/Phillies
        Joe Nuxhall/Cincinnati
        Wayne Krenczicki/Cincinnati
        Tony Perez/ Cincinnati
      - Interviews, 1985 February 26-June 25 (Offsite-box 4124, Item 87-99)
        Jerry Lucas/basketball Hall of Famer
        Frank Shorter/1972 Olympic Marathon champion
        Johnny Podres/Minnesota Twins
        Gary Carter/New York Mets
        Dean Meminger/New York Knicks former player
        Wayne Gretzky/Edmonton Oilers
        Bryan Trottier/New York Islanders
        Dale Hawerchuk/Winnipeg Jets
        Glen Hanlon/New York Rangers
        Bobby Carpenter/Washington Capitals
        Joe Dimaggio/New York Yankees Hall of Famer
        Don Nelson/Milwaukee Bucks coach
        Glenn Gunningham/1928-1940 track star
        Artis Gilmore/San Antonio Spurs
        George Mikan/basketball Hall of Famer
        Quinn Buckner/Boston Celtics
        Joe Mullaney/Providence College basketball coach
        Jo-Jo Townsell/Los Angeles Express wide receiver
        Donald Trump/New Jersey Generals owner
        Alton Lister/Milwaukee Bucks
        Kevin McHale/Boston Celtics
        George Gervin/San Antonio Spurs
        Rick Barry/former pro basketball star
        Alvan Adams/Phoenix Suns
        Kerry Justin/New Jersey Generals cornerback
        Pete Rose/Cincinnati Reds player and manager
        Willie Randolph/New York Yankees
        Bruce Hurst/Boston Red Sox
        Tim Kerr/Philadelphia Flyers
        Richard Johnson/Houston Gamblers slotback
        Hershell Walker/New Jersey Generals running back
        Rod Foster/Phoenix Suns
        Omar Moreno/New York Yankees
        Jim Kelly/Houston Gamblers quarterback
        Bill Campbell/St. Louis Cardinals
        Mel Stottlemyre/New York Mets coach
        Joe Price/Cincinnati Reds
        Tom Seaver/Chicago White Sox
        Phil Rizzuto/New York Yankees broadcaster
        Mel Hall/Cleveland Indians
        Steve Palermo/American League umpire
        Jim Rice/Boston Red Sox
        Chuck Tanner/Pittsburgh Pirates
        Howard Johnson/New York Mets
        Jerry Reuss/Los Angeles Dodgers
        Rocky Bridges/San Francisco Giants coach
        Bud Harrelson/New York Mets coach
        Jim Davenport/San Francisco Giants manager
        Don Sutton/Oakland Athletics
        Ricky Henderson/New York Yankees
        Tom Brookens/Detroit Tigers
        Willie Upshaw/Toronto Blue Jays
        Keith Moreland/Chicago Cub
        Willie McGee/St. Louis Cardinals
      - Interviews, 1985 July 15-October 8 (Offsite-box 4125, Item 1-10)
        Dave Krieg/Seattle Seahawks quarterback
        Kim Bokamper/Miami Dolphins
        Willie Stargell/Pittsburgh Pirates coach
        Bob Cousey/Boston Celtics Hall of Famer
        Jon Miller/radio voice of Baltimore Orioles
        Steve Largent/Seattle Seahawks wide receiver
        Louis Lipps/Pittsburgh Steelers wide receiver
        Elgin Baylor/Los Angeles Lakers Hall of Fame
        Hubert Green/golf pro
        Pete Vukovich/Milwaukee Brewers
        Phile Nierko/New York Yankees
        Neal Heaton/Cleveland Indians
        Andy Etchebarren/Milwaukee Brewers coach
        Ken Kaiser/American League umpire
        Tom Kite/gold pro Von Hayes/Philadelphia Phillies
        Bill Robinson/New York Mets coach
        Lyle Alzado/Los Angeles Raiders
        Joe Frazier/former heavyweight champ
        Wille Randolph/New York Yankees
        Joe Youngblood/San Francisco Giants
        Bruce Froemming/National League umpire
        John Spagnola/Philadelphia Eagles tight end
        Orel Hershier/Los Angeles Dodgers
        John Candelaria/California Angels
        Ed Lopat/former New York Yankees star
        Pat Day/all star jockey
        Cab Calloway/celebrity sport
        Mark Gastinaeu/New York Jets
        Fred Smerlas/Buffalo Bills nose tackle
        Vince Coleman/St. Louis Cardinals
        Tim Flannery/San Diego Padres
        Bob Forsch/St/ Louis Cardinals
        Bobby Cox/Toronto Blue Jays manager
        Herman Edwards/Philadelphia Eagles defensive back
        Elois Grooms/St. Louis Cardinals defensive tackle
        Bod Pellegrini/former Philadelphia Eagles star
        Cal Ripken, Jr./Baltimore Orioles
        Jeff Torborg/New York Yankees coach
        Kirk McCaskill/California Angels
        Phil Bradley/Seattle Mariners
        Rick Manning/Milwaukee Brewers
        Marty Lyons/New York Jets defensive end
        Harry Carson/New York Giants linebacker
        Dextor Clinkscale/Dallas Cowboys defensive back
      - Interviews, 1985 December 26 (Offsite-box 4126, Item 5)
        Kareem Abdul Jabbar (Sportsman of the Year 1985)
      - Interviews, 1986 October 29 (Offsite-box 4126, Item 6)
        Andy Bathgate
        Ken Houston
        Harby Howell
        Bobby Doerr
        Doak Walker
        Fred Taylor
        Don Budge
      - Interviews, undated (Offsite-box 4125, Item 24-26)
        Micki King
        Karen Rogers
        Wyomia Tyus
      - Interviews, undated (Offsite-box 4126, Item 7)
        Paul Hornun
        Rocky Bleier
        Walt Frazier
        Brooks Robinson
        Gaylord Perry
        Enos Slaughter
        Dick Butkus
        Al Unser
        Micki King Hogue
      - Interviews, undated (Offsite-box 4126, Item 8)
        Sports Illustrated (illegible)
        (illegible)
        Family Ties
        Good Sports
      - Probable Morris Interviews, 1983-1985 (Offsite-box 4127, Item 1)
        Emerson Booser
        Carol Alt
        Ron Greschner
      - Probable Morris Interviews, 1983 (Offsite-box 4127, Item 2)
        Gary Matthews
        Lou Piniella
        Tippy Martinez
      - Probable Morris Interviews, 1983-1984 (Offsite-box 4127, Item 3)
        Glen Hanlon
        Mark Pavelich
      - Probable Morris Interviews, 1983-1984 (Offsite-box 4127, Item 4)
        Arthur Reichert
        Laura Stamm
        Anders Hedberg
        Pierre Larouche
        Mark Osborne
        Don Maloney
        Tom Laidlaw
      - Probable Morris Interviews, 1985 December 17 (Offsite-box 4127, Item 5)
        Kareem Abdul-Jabaar (Sportsman of the Year)
      - Probable Morris Interviews, 1985 December 17 (Offsite-box 4127, Item 6)
      - Probable Morris Interviews, 1985 December 17 (Offsite-box 4127, Item 7)
    - Subsubseries VI.A.5. Promotional Audiovisual Files, 1936?-1980?; 5.1 Linear feet in 5 record cartons and 1 document case
      Records include primarily audiovisual recordings of sporting events or contests and sports instructional films with some accompanying papers. The bulk of the records date from 1954 to 1967. Papers include form letters describing the films and response cards for the recipient to return regarding use of the film. The 1967 Sportsman of the Year contains a full collection of response cards. The files in box 4128 contain materials addressed to and from Terry Rice. Some of the audiovisual is part of the Sports Illustrated tape service based on the papers.
      Organized chronologically based on the original order with "How To" films at the end.
      - Olympic Film, 1936 or 1980 (Offsite-box 4128, Folder 1)
        1 film reel; 16mm. On container: An L.A. Olympic Committee 1980 sticker over a label that says "Dictaphone version-_____ 1936-Olympic film."
      - AIGA Meeting [American Institute of Graphic Arts?], 1954 December 1 (Offsite-box 4128, Folder 2)
        1 audiotape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips; 7 in., 1/4 in. tape. On container: "Reel No. 1. AIGA Dinner."
        1 audiotape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips; 7 in., 1/4 in. tape. On container: "Reel No. 2. Advertising Club AIGA meeting."
      - Kentucky Derby Film Release, 1955 (Offsite-box 4128, Folder 3)
      - US Open, 1955 (Offsite-box 4128, Folder 4)
      - Hungarian Fencing and Gymnasts, circa 1955 (Offsite-box 4128, Folder 5)
        1 film reel; 16mm. On container: "Fencers and gymnasts. Milwaikee, Wisconsin February 10-11." On reel: "Hungarian fencing at YMCA."
        1 film reel; 16mm. On container: "Our film both teams."
      - Bonnie Prudden "How to Keep Fit" Record, circa 1957 (Offsite-box 4128, Folder 6)
        Includes audiovisual material as part of a trifold brochure.
        1 phonograph record (33 rpm); 7 1/2 in.
      - Sportsman of the Year: Rafer Johnson, 1958 (Offsite-box 4128, Folder 7)
        1 film reel; 16mm. On container: "Rafer J. SOY film - 1958."
      - Sports Illustrated Design Awards, 1959 (Offsite-box 4128, Folder 8)
        1 film reel; 16mm. On container: "SIDA film clip."
        1 film reel; 16mm. On note: "Fashions or Fabrics. No idea."
      - Sportsman of the Year: Johansson, 1959 (Offsite-box 4128, Folder 9)
        1 film reel; 16mm. from Allend'or Productions Spotlite News.
      - Richard A. Knight, 1950s? (Offsite-box 4128, Folder 10)
        1 metal casing audiocassette (used in Mohawk Midgetape portable recorder): analog, 1/4 in. tape.
        1 audiotape reel: analog; 5 in., 1/4 in. tape.
      - Sport Show Col____, 1950s? (Offsite-box 4146, Item 2)
      - Television Film on U.S. Open (Golf tournament) Preview, 1961 June (Offsite-box 4129, Folder 1-2)
        1 film reel; 16mm. On reel: "Alex Colt." A note to Colt with the reel states it is an extra print of an interview with Player and Palmer.
      - Track Star Television Film, 1961 July (Offsite-box 4129, Folder 3-4)
        1 film reel; 16mm. On reel: "AAU track stars."
      - Tennis Television Film, 1961 August (Offsite-box 4129, Folder 5-6)
      - Film Interview with Football Coaches, 1961 September (Offsite-box 4129, Folder 7-8)
      - World Series Preview, 1961 September (Offsite-box 4129, Folder 9-10)
      - 1961 Sportsman of the Year Film, 1962 January (Offsite-box 4129, Folder 11-12)
        1 film reel; 16mm. On container: "Sportsman of Year and 1961 highlight film. 4 minutes (16 mm. sound). Property of Keith Morris."
      - Pole Vault Special Film, 1962 February (Offsite-box 4129, Folder 13-14)
      - Spring Training Film, 1962 April (Offsite-box 4129, Folder 15-16)
        1 film reel; 16mm. On container: "1962 Baseball Preview (running time 10 min. 41 sec.). 16mm. sound. Rocky Colavito. Casey Stengel. Roger Maris. Jim O'Toole. Wally Moon."
        1 film reel; 16mm. On tape: "B. Robinson."
      - Kentucky Derby Film, 1962 April (Offsite-box 4129, Folder 17-18)
      - U.S. Open (Golf tournament) Film, 1962 June (Offsite-box 4129, Folder 19-20)
        1 film reel; 16mm. On tape: "Player and Palmer."
      - Sonny Liston Film Interview, 1962 September (Offsite-box 4129, Folder 21)
      - College Football Coaches Film, 1963 (Offsite-box 4130, Folder 1-3)
        2 film reels; 16mm.
      - 1963 Sportsman of the Year Film (Offsite-box 4130, Folder 4-5)
      - Spring Training Film, 1963 (Offsite-box 4130, Folder 6-7)
        1 film reel; 16mm. On container: "Filmed interviews with baseball players prior to the 1963 season. Mailed 3-29-63."
      - World Series Preview Film, 1963 (Offsite-box 4130, Folder 8-9)
      - Kentucky Derby Film, 1963 April (Offsite-box 4130, Folder 10-11)
        1 film reel; 16mm. On reel: "Filmed interview with Willie Shoemaker and some footage on Never Bend prior to the Kentucky Derbey - Mailed 4-24-63."
      - U.S. Open (Golf tournament) Film, 1963 June (Offsite-box 4130, Folder 12-13)
        1 film reel; 16mm. On reel: "Filmed interview with Jack Nicklaus and Tony Lema - U.S. Open preview. Mailed 6-12-63."
      - Baseball Preview Film, 1964 (Offsite-box 4130, Folder 14-15)
      - Football Film, 1964 (Offsite-box 4130, Folder 16-17)
      - Proposed Highlight Film for Sports Illustrated Tenth Anniversary, 1964 (Offsite-box 4130, Folder 18)
      - Sonny Liston and Cassius Clay Film, 1964 February (Offsite-box 4130, Folder 19)
      - Kentucky Derby Preview Film, 1964 April (Offsite-box 4130, Folder 20)
      - U.S. Open (Golf tournament) Film, 1964 June (Offsite-box 4131, Folder 1-2)
      - World's Fair Film, 1964 August (Offsite-box 4131, Folder 3)
        1 film reel; 16mm. On reel: "Sports Illustrated at the fair."
      - Sportsman of the Year Award, 1964 December (Offsite-box 4131, Folder 4-5)
      - Baseball Preview Film, 1965 (Offsite-box 4131, Folder 6-7)
      - Kentucky Derby Preview Film, 1965 (Offsite-box 4131, Folder 8)
      - 1965 Sportsman of the Year Film: Sandy Koufax (Offsite-box 4131, Folder 9-10)
      - World Series Preview Film, 1965 (Offsite-box 4131, Folder 11-12)
      - U.S. Open (Golf tournament) Preview, 1965 June (Offsite-box 4131, Folder 13-14)
      - College Football Coaches, 1965 September (Offsite-box 4131, Folder 15-16)
      - Golf Films, 1966 (Offsite-box 4132, Folder 1)
      - Kentucky Derby Film, 1966 (Offsite-box 4132, Folder 2-3)
      - Spring Training Film, 1966 (Offsite-box 4132, Folder 4)
      - U.S. Open Golf Preview Film, 1966 (Offsite-box 4132, Folder 5)
      - Hilton Film: Baseball Film Mailing, 1967 (Offsite-box 4132, Folder 6)
      - 1967 Sportsman of the Year Film Clip: Carl Yastrzemski (Offsite-box 4132, Folder 7-8)
        1 film reel; 16mm. On tape: "Office copy 1967 Sportsman Carl Yastrzemski."
      - "How To" Films: Baseball: Al Downing, 1966 (Offsite-box 4132, Folder 9-10)
      - "How To" Films: Baseball: Brooks Robinson, 1966 (Offsite-box 4132, Folder 11)
      - "How To" Films: Baseball: Tom Tresh, 1967 (Offsite-box 4132, Folder 12)
      - "How To" Films: Basketball: Bill Sharman, 1967 (Offsite-box 4132, Folder 13-14)
      - "How To" Films: Golf: Dave Marr and Mike Souchak, 1966 (Offsite-box 4132, Folder 15)
      - "How To" Films: Horseback Riding: Gordon Wright, 1966 (Offsite-box 4132, Folder 16-17)
  - Subseries VI.A. Publicity Director Jane Gilchrist Files, 1950s-1989; 5.5 Linear feet in 6 record cartons and 1 flat box
    Jane Gilchrist joined Time Inc. as an Sports Illustrated (SI) production assistant in 1955. She is first listed in the Department Heads Lists in 1976 as the Press Information Director. From 1979 to 1987, she holds the title of Publicity Director, taking over part of Keith Morris's position. A September 1972 article from the staff newsletter FYI announced her promotion to promotion manager of Time-Life Video after serving five years at the SI direct mail manager although her files indicate she returned to SI soon after.
    "On the Move," FYI, September 18, 1972.
    Jane Gilchrist's files document her work organizing or publicizing Sports Illustrated (SI) events. Specifically, Gilchrist's files document: her planning and publicizing of events related to SI's 20th and 25th anniversary, including researching the history of SI for background material; work done by SI to produced and distributed the official souvenir program for the 1984 Los Angeles Olympics; SI's 1986 poll on American's attitudes towards sports and athletes; publicity around announcements of the Sportsman and Sportswoman of the Year; publicity regarding the swimsuit covers; and Time Inc.'s trial run working on the magazine Women's Sports & Fitness (WSF). The majority of records are correspondence, magazine issues, press releases, press conference notes and invites, press kits, and photographic material of events.
    Items of interest include a videotape of an interview with editor Julie Campbell on the evolution of the swimsuit cover for a news segment on swimwear and a letter in WSF Media Lists from Billie Jean King containing her comments on the business relationship between SI and WSF.
    Organized alphabetically with arrangement imposed by the archivist. Files originally found mainly grouped by topic such as Olympics, Swimsuit, Poll, and Women's Sports & Fitness.
    - Anniversaries: Background Research: Basic Materials, 1950s-1970s (Offsite-box 4133, Folder 1)
    - Anniversaries: Background Research: Cover Jinx, 1979 (Offsite-box 4133, Folder 2)
    - Anniversaries: Background Research: Elson Chapter from Time Inc. History, 1979? (Offsite-box 4133, Folder 3)
    - Anniversaries: Background Research: Important Speeches, 1955-1975 (Offsite-box 4133, Folder 4-5)
    - Anniversaries: 10th Anniversary: News Clips, 1964 (Offsite-box 4133, Folder 6)
    - Anniversaries: 20th Anniversary: Business Information, 1974 (Offsite-box 4133, Folder 7)
    - Anniversaries: 20th Anniversary: Charter Employees, 1974? (Offsite-box 4133, Folder 8)
    - Anniversaries: 20th Anniversary: Clips, 1971-1974 (Offsite-box 4133, Folder 9)
    - Anniversaries: 20th Anniversary: Correspondence, 1974 (Offsite-box 4133, Folder 10)
    - Anniversaries: 20th Anniversary: Party, 1974 (Offsite-box 4133, Folder 11)
    - Anniversaries: 20th Anniversary: Photographs, [1974] (Offsite-box 4133, Folder 12)
    - Anniversaries: 20th Anniversary: Speeches and General Information, 1974 (Offsite-box 4133, Folder 13)
    - Anniversaries: 25th Anniversary: Circulation and Pormotion Information, 1979 (Offsite-box 4133, Folder 14)
    - Anniversaries: 25th Anniversary: Cities: Akron, 1979 (Offsite-box 4133, Folder 15)
    - Anniversaries: 25th Anniversary: Cities: Boston, 1979 (Offsite-box 4133, Folder 16)
    - Anniversaries: 25th Anniversary: Cities: Chicago, 1979 (Offsite-box 4133, Folder 17)
      1 audiocassette: analog; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape.
    - Anniversaries: 25th Anniversary: Cities: Dallas, 1980 (Offsite-box 4133, Folder 18)
    - Anniversaries: 25th Anniversary: Cities: Detroit, 1979 (Offsite-box 4133, Folder 19)
    - Anniversaries: 25th Anniversary: Cities: Hartford, [1979] (Offsite-box 4133, Folder 20)
    - Anniversaries: 25th Anniversary: Cities: Houston, 1979 (Offsite-box 4133, Folder 21)
    - Anniversaries: 25th Anniversary: Cities: Los Angeles, 1979 (Offsite-box 4133, Folder 22)
    - Anniversaries: 25th Anniversary: Cities: Milwaukee: First Cover Reshoot, 1979 (Offsite-box 4133, Folder 23-24)
    - Anniversaries: 25th Anniversary: Cities: New York, 1979 (Offsite-box 4133, Folder 25)
    - Anniversaries: 25th Anniversary: Cities: Pittsburgh, 1979 (Offsite-box 4133, Folder 26)
    - Anniversaries: 25th Anniversary: Cities: Rochester, 1979 (Offsite-box 4133, Folder 27)
    - Anniversaries: 25th Anniversary: Cities: St. Louis, 1979 (Offsite-box 4133, Folder 28)
    - Anniversaries: 25th Anniversary: Cities: Washington, D.C.: Dinner, 1979 (Offsite-box 4133, Folder 29-30)
    - Anniversaries: 25th Anniversary: Cities: Washington, D.C. and New York City: Photographs, [1979] (Offsite-box 4133, Folder 31)
    - Anniversaries: 25th Anniversary: Cities: Washington, D.C.: Press Conference, 1979 (Offsite-box 4134, Folder 1)
    - Anniversaries: 25th Anniversary: Cities: Winston-Salem, 1979 (Offsite-box 4134, Folder 2)
    - Anniversaries: 25th Anniversary: Press Clips, 1979 (Offsite-box 4134, Folder 3-5)
    - Anniversaries: 25th Anniversary: FYI Article, [1979] (Offsite-box 4134, Folder 6)
    - Anniversaries: 25th Anniversary: Letters, 1978-1979 (Offsite-box 4134, Folder 7)
    - Anniversaries: 25th Anniversary: Rate Information, 1979 (Offsite-box 4134, Folder 8)
    - Anniversaries: 25th Anniversary: Smithsonian Sportsman of the Year Exhibition, 1979 (Offsite-box 4134, Folder 9)
    - Anniversaries: 25th Anniversary: Show Schedule, 1979 (Offsite-box 4134, Folder 10)
    - Anniversaries: 25th Anniversary: Trivia Quiz, 1979 (Offsite-box 4134, Folder 11)
    - Anniversaries: 25th Anniversary: "25 Years of Photographs", [1979] (Offsite-box 4134, Folder 12)
    - Baseball Issue Mailing, 1987-1988 (Offsite-box 4134, Folder 13)
    - Catfish Book: Jim Hunter and Armen Keteyan, 1988 (Offsite-box 4134, Folder 14)
    - Fast Copy/Ohlmeyer Communications, 1986 (Offsite-box 4134, Folder 15)
    - Home Box Office (HBO) Film Library, 1986 (Offsite-box 4134, Folder 16)
    - Howlett, Philip G., 1986 (Offsite-box 4134, Folder 17)
    - Melpomene Institute, 1988 (Offsite-box 4134, Folder 18)
    - National Public Radio, 1979-1982 (Offsite-box 4134, Folder 19-21)
      2 audiocassettes: analog; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. Label on container: "Sports Sampler from NPR's Morning Edition" dated 1982.
    - Olympics: 1980: Invitation to Gerald Ford, 1977 (Offsite-box 4134, Folder 22)
    - Olympics: 1984: Preview Issue of Sports Illustrated (Offsite-box 4134, Folder 23-26)
    - Olympics: 1984: Printed Program (Offsite-box 4135, Folder 1-2)
    - Olympics: 1984: Sagafjord Party (Offsite-box 4135, Folder 3-4)
    - Olympics: 1988: Pathway to the Olympics Manual, 1987 (Offsite-box 4135, Folder 5)
    - Poll: General, 1986 (Offsite-box 4135, Folder 6)
    - Poll: Bronner, Judy, 1986 (Offsite-box 4135, Folder 7)
    - Poll: Columnists, 1986 (Offsite-box 4135, Folder 8)
    - Poll: Expenses, 1986 (Offsite-box 4135, Folder 9)
    - Poll: Invitation and Copy, 1986 (Offsite-box 4135, Folder 10-11)
    - Poll: Panel, 1986 (Offsite-box 4135, Folder 12)
    - Poll: Press Conference, 1986 (Offsite-box 4135, Folder 13)
    - Poll: Requests, 1986 (Offsite-box 4135, Folder 14)
    - Poll: Ruder Finn [empty], [1986] (Offsite-box 4135, Folder 15)
    - Poll: Top 50 [Markets? US?], 1986 (Offsite-box 4135, Folder 16)
    - Poll: Top 50 [Markets? US?], 1986 (Offsite-box 4147, Folder 3)
    - Radio City Music Hall 50th Birthday, 1981 (Offsite-box 4135, Folder 17)
    - Sportsman/Sportswoman of the Year: 1976: Chris Evert (Offsite-box 4136, Folder 1)
    - Sportsman/Sportswoman of the Year: 1977: Steve Cauthen (Offsite-box 4136, Folder 2)
    - Sportsman/Sportswoman of the Year: 1978: Jack Nicklaus (Offsite-box 4136, Folder 3)
    - Sportsman/Sportswoman of the Year: 1979: Terry Bradshaw and Willie Stargell (Offsite-box 4136, Folder 4)
    - Sportsman/Sportswoman of the Year: 1980: U.S. Olympic Hockey Team (Offsite-box 4136, Folder 5)
    - Sportsman/Sportswoman of the Year: 1981: Sugar Ray Leonard (Offsite-box 4136, Folder 6)
    - Sportsman/Sportswoman of the Year: 1982: Wayne Gretzky (Offsite-box 4136, Folder 7)
    - Sportsman/Sportswoman of the Year: 1983: Mary Decker (Offsite-box 4136, Folder 8-9)
    - Sportsman/Sportswoman of the Year: 1984: Edwin Moses and Mary Lou Retton (Offsite-box 4136, Folder 10-11)
    - Sportsman/Sportswoman of the Year: 1985: Kareem Abdul-Jabbar (Offsite-box 4136, Folder 12-13)
    - Sportsman/Sportswoman of the Year: Joe Paterno, 1986 (Offsite-box 4136, Folder 14-15)
    - Swimsuit Cover: 1986: News Clippings (Offsite-box 4135, Folder 18-20)
    - Swimsuit Cover: 1987: Good Morning America, 1987-1988 (Offsite-box 4135, Folder 21)
    - Swimsuit Cover: 1988: General, 1987-1988 (Offsite-box 4135, Folder 22-24)
      1 videocassette (VHS) (60 min.): 1/2 in. On container: "'Market Focus' Womens May/June '87."